Best Friends Take the Stage and Steal the Show!
Bratz: Rock Angelz is a animation, family, music
film directed by David Mucci Fassett.
After starting up their own teen magazine, Bratz girls Yasmin, Cloe,
Jade, and Sasha fly to London to cover a rock concert.
Yasmin (voice), played by Dionne Quan.
Cloe (voice), played by Olivia Hack.
Jade (voice), played by Soleil Moon Frye.
Sasha (voice), played by Tia Mowry.
Burdine Maxwell (voice), played by Wendie Malick.
Kirstee (voice), played by Kaley Cuoco.
Bratz: Rock Angelz is a 2005 adventure video game based on the
Bratz fashion doll line and published by THQ.
It is based on the direct-to-video film Bratz: Rock Angelz and
the line of dolls affiliated with the same name.
The game was released for the PlayStation 2,
GameCube, Game Boy Advance, and Windows.
Blitz Games developed the PlayStation 2 and GameCube versions, while Altron and AWE
Games developed the Game Boy Advance and Windows versions respectively.
The game loosely follows the film's plot, where
the Bratz start a fashion magazine.
They later receive an invitation from a nightclub in London to perform at a
concert venue and outsell their rival competitor, Your Thing magazine.
However, unlike the film, the Bratz travel to areas other than London.
The gameplay primarily revolves around participating in tasks for
the magazine, as well as performing fashion shows.
It also features a variety of minigames that consist
of posing, photography, and racing.
Players can also dress the Bratz girls in various fashion
lines and apply makeup to their faces.
Upon release, reviews of Bratz: Rock Angelz were generally mixed.
Some critics praised the game for its open world,
minigames, and creative features.
However, many others criticized it for its sole
appeal to a young female demographic.
The game sold 1.5 million copies upon its release.
It also received three sequels, which are titled Bratz: Forever Diamondz (2006),
Bratz: The Movie (2007), and Bratz: Girlz Really Rock (2008).